哦
Oh.
你在乒乓球桌上痛宰麦克 真让我兴奋 你要不要…
The way you crushed Mike at Ping-Pong was such a turn-on. You wanna?
我很想 但是我有点累
You know, I'd love to, but I'm a little tired.
- 那我把枕头套盖在头上   - 我们来吧
- I'll put a pillowcase over my head.    - You're on.
- 两位   - 怎么了？
- Hey.    - What's up?
麦克在洗澡 顺便一提 洗澡不犯法
Well, Mike's taking a shower, which, by the way, there's no law against.
我们等一下要去吃点东西 所以你们要不要…
And, um, then we're gonna grab some food. So if you want...
- 终于   - 那是罗斯吗？
- Finally.    - Is that Ross?
对 这面烂墙 隔壁发生什么事 都可以听得到
Yeah. You can hear everything through these stupid walls.
- 他好像有同伴   - 他也有可能是自己一个人
- Sounds like he's with someone.    - He could be alone.
今早我听到他在做伏地挺身的时候 跟自己的三头肌说话
This morning I heard him do pushups and then talk to his triceps.
等等 我想菲比说对了
Wait a minute, I think Phoebe's right.
对 我听到他的房间里有别人
Yeah, I hear someone else in there with him.
哦
Oh.
- 盖勒博士   - 天啊 你真是太棒了
- Dr. Geller!     - God, you're amazing.
我竟然不需要请你 叫我盖勒博士
I didn't even have to ask you to call me that.
- 我的天啊 那是查莉   - 她竟然背着乔伊跟罗斯偷情
- Oh, my God, that's Charlie!    - She's cheating on Joey with Ross!
这个又烂 又淫荡 女巨人
Oh, that tart! Floozy! Giant!
- 我不太确定这样对不对   - 对 没错
- I'm not sure about this.     - Yeah, you're right.
这根本不关我们的事
This is none of our business.
我不确定这样能不能听清楚一切 快拿个玻璃杯给我
I'm not sure it's the best way to hear everything. Get me a glass!
不 我才不要这样做 我不要偷听朋友的隐私
No, I'm not gonna do this, okay? I'm not gonna eavesdrop on my friend.
我爱巴贝多
Ha, ha. I love Barbados.
- 真不敢相信我正在吻你   - 哈 哈
- I can't believe I'm kissing you.    - Ha, ha.
- 我在吻瑞秋   - 哈哈
- I'm kissing Rachel!    - Ha, ha.
- 我知道 我就是瑞秋   - 哦
- I know. I'm her. Ha, ha.    - Oh!
瑞秋跟乔伊 是瑞秋跟乔伊
Rachel and Joey! It's Rachel and Joey!
- 什么？ - 过来这里
- What?   - Get over here!
- 哦   - 哇哦
- Oh.   - Whoa!
天啊 我爱死这些薄墙壁了
Oh, my God! I love how thin these walls are!
谢谢
Thank you.
--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制:呆呆熊  字幕来源:原盘中字  调校:悠悠  招募Q号:76846146
之前你说我们之间不会有什么的 为什么改变了？
Hey, before, you said that nothing could happen between us. What changed?
- 我因为罗斯才那样说的   - 嗯
- Well, I only said that because of Ross.   - Mm.
- 但我看到他亲了查莉   - 什么？
- And then I saw him kissing Charlie.    - What?
罗斯跟查莉？
Ross and Charlie?
哇… 她还真的在努力融入这个小团体
Wow! She's really making her way through the group, huh?
- 算了 我有什么资格说她   - 没错
- Ah, who am I to talk? Ha, ha.     - Yeah.
真是不敢相信 瑞秋跟乔伊？
I can't believe this. Rachel and Joey?
那么另一间的恐龙双胞胎又如何？
How about the dinosaur twins in the other room?
- 那一边没有人顾了   - 我来顾
- No one is manning that wall!    - I'm on it!
- 有动静吗？ - 我好像听到窗帘拉上的声音
- Anything?  - I think I hear curtains closing.
我这里听到鞋子被踢掉的声音
We've got shoes being kicked off over here.
床里面的弹簧 绝对不会错
Bedsprings! Unmistakable!
- 你知道那是你哥哥吗？ - 你说了我才知道 谁来跟我换边
- You realize that's your brother.  - Not until you said it. Somebody switch!
等等 等一下
Wow! Wait a minute.
罗斯跟查莉 乔伊跟瑞秋
Ross and Charlie. Joey and Rachel.
菲比跟麦克 我们是唯一 到这里来…
Phoebe and Mike. We're the only ones leaving with the person we came with!
不对 我跟摩妮卡一起来 但我会跟搞怪艾尔回去
That's not true. I came with Monica, I'm leaving with Weird Al.
够了 别再笑我的头发了
Okay, I've had it with the hair jokes.
- 我明天离开前就去发廊   - 是的 蓦麦小姐
- Tomorrow I'm going to the salon.     - Okay, Buckwheat.
你们一定要过来听听 好像是免费的色情片一样
You gotta hear this, it's great! It's like free porn.
呃…
Um...
- 你还好吗？ - 只是… 我想我不能这么做
- Is everything okay?  - It's just... I don't think I can do this.
是因为床罩的关系吗？
Oh, is it because of what might be on the bed?
- 我看过报导 有红外线… - 不 不是
- I saw that report, with the infrared...  - No! No.
不是
No, uh...
我必须跟乔伊谈谈 你们才刚分手而已
Look, I need to talk to Joey. I mean, you guys just broke up.
在我们进行下一步之前 我必须知道他的确不在意
Before anything more happens between us, I need to know he's okay with it.
- 我完全了解   - 好 那我去找他
- I, uh, completely understand.    - All right, I'm gonna go find him.
在去之前 我必须准备一下 你知道…
I just need a second before I can, you know...
奶奶…
Grandma, Grandma, Grandma.
- 好 回头见   - 好
- Okay, I'll see you later.    - Okay!
关门的声音 他走了
That's the door. He's gone.
她开了电视
And she's turning on the TV...
正在看…《麻辣女王》
...and watching Miss Congeniality.
亲爱的 如果隔着墙都听得出来 你对那部戏就太熟了
Honey? If you know it through a wall, you know it too well.
嘿 你们在干什么？
Hey, what are you guys doing?
我们…很难过要离开了 所以正在跟旅馆道别
Oh, we're just... We're sad to go, so we're just saying goodbye to the hotel.
我爱你
I love you...
天堂饭店高尔夫水疗度假村
...Paradise Hotel Golf Resort and Spa.
我们玩得很开心 谢谢你
Yeah. We had a great time, thank you.
再见
Bye.
好 你们有看到乔伊吗？
Okay. Um, hey, have you guys seen Joey anywhere?
他搞不好在房间里 跟现任女朋友查莉在一起
He's probably in his room with his current girlfriend, Charlie.
我们只知道这种情况
That's the situation as we know it.
如果你们看到他 可以告诉他 我在找他吗？
If you see him, could you tell him I'm looking for him?
- 没问题   - 谢谢
- You got it.    - Thanks.
谢谢
Thank you.
另一面墙 两位 另一面墙
Other wall, people! Other wall!
- 瑞秋 你在吗？ - 天啊 是罗斯
- Rach, you there?     - Oh, my God, that's Ross!
- 我们要怎么办？ - 好 冷静一点
- What are we gonna do?    - Okay, just be calm.
他只需要知道 我们两个碰巧在一起就行了
For all he knows, we're just hanging out.
好吗？ 表现出漠不关心的样子
All right? So just be nonchalant.
- 那不是漠不关心的样子   - 我不懂那是什么意思
- That's not nonchalant!    - No idea what it means.
好吧 去躲起来就好
Okay, just hide.
- 瑞秋？ - 我来了 试试床底下吧
- Rach?    - Coming! Try under the bed.
床底下没有空间…
There's no room under the bed...
- 切都还好吗？ - 很好
- Is everything okay?    - Yeah.
- 嘿 你知道乔伊在哪里吗？ - 嗨
- Hey. Do you know where Joey is?    - Hi.
我真的不知道
I really don't.
- 可以跟你谈谈吗？ - 当然可以
- Can I talk to you for a minute?    - Yeah. Sure.
真是不敢相信
I don't believe this.
- 你们一直在…   - 墙的这一边是用来听的
- Have you guys been...?    - Shh! This is the listening side of the wall.
然后她告诉我 她跟乔伊分手了
Then she told me that she and Joey had broken up...
而其中一个原因是 她对我有特别的感觉
...and part of the reason was she had feelings for me.
是吗？
Uh-huh, right. Yeah.
你也知道从见面的那一天 我就一直想约查莉出去
You know I've wanted to ask Charlie out since the day I met her.
我知道…你真的很为难
Oh, I know, I know. That's been really hard for you.
算了 事情一直发展下去
Anyway, one thing led to another, and...
不知不觉中 我们就接吻了
...oh, before you know it, we were kissing.
你觉得乔伊会有多生气？
How angry do you think Joey's gonna be?
很难说 罗斯 真的很难说
That is hard to say, Ross. That is hard to say.
我一定得找到他 他一定在这里的某处吧
I gotta find him. He's gotta be here someplace.
应该是吧
You would think.
乔伊
Joey?
- 他走了吗？ - 你是怎么办到的？
- Is he gone?    - How are you doing this?
喂
Psst!
怎么？这是怎么回事
What? Hey!
你们在干什么？ 你们一直都在偷听吗？
What are you...? What is this? Have you been listening this entire time?
对
Yeah!
你们是怎么回事？
Now, what is this?
怎么回事？ 让我想想 我们亲吻了大概十分钟
What is this? Well, let's see. We kissed for 10 minutes...
然后告诉我们的朋友 我想我们好像还在念小学六年级
...and now we're talking to our friends about it, so I guess this is sixth grade.
你们有想过情况会变得多么复杂吗？
No, no. Have you thought about how complicated this could get?
- 那么罗斯怎么办？ - 他现在跟查莉在- 起了
- What about Ross?    - Well, he's with Charlie now.
对 但他在进行下一步之前 想要跟你谈谈
Yeah, but he wants to talk to you before anything really happens with her.
身为朋友 你不觉得 自己也应该做相同的事情吗？
And as his friend, I mean, don't you think he deserves the same from you?
盖勒 你真是太难搞了
You're a pain in my ass, Geller.
各位 我们很成谢所有的建议
Look, we appreciate all the advice...
但这是我跟乔伊的事情 我们可以自己处理的
...but this is between Joey and me. We can handle it.
好 但是可不可以 为关心你的人做一件事？
We'll go. Will you do one thing for us, the people that care about you?
- 当然可以   - 发音清楚一点
- Sure.    - Enunciate.
滚出去
Get out!
他们是对的吗？
Are they right?
可能吧 我们也许应该…
Probably, yeah. I mean, maybe we should...
在跟罗斯谈过之前先等一等
...hold off until we talk to Ross.
也是 我们可以等的 又不是今晚一定要有什么事发生
Yeah. Yeah. We can wait. We don't have to do anything tonight.
对 我想这样最好
Yeah, I think that would be best.
所以我…我要走了
So, I'm gonna... I'm gonna take off.
- 然而…   - 我喜欢这个"然而"
- Although...    - I like "although."
- 额   - 我是说 你知道…
- Uh...    - I mean, you know...
罗斯跟我已经没在一起…
Ross and I haven't dated in, like...
六年了吧
...six years.
六年了？
Six years?
跟读高中的时间差不多长了
Wow. That's almost as long as high school.
再说 他现在跟查莉在一起
Plus, you know, he is with Charlie now.
没错
Absolutely.
- 他根本没把你当一回事   - 才没有
- He's not thinking about you.     - No.
我把你当一回事
I'm thinking about you.
是
Yeah.
- 我们把罗斯给忘了吧   - 早就忘了
- Let's forget about Ross.     - It's forgotten.
- 怎么了？ - 没事
- What's wrong?    - Nothing.
说真的 到底怎么了？
Seriously, what is it?
没事 真的…真的没事 来吧
Nothing. It's really... It's nothing. Come here. Come here.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
对不起 我…
Ah. Sorry, I just, um...
我无法把罗斯从脑子里赶出去
I can't seem to get Ross out of my head.
也许我能帮你
Well, maybe I can help.
你的嘴唇真软 再来一次吧
Your lips are so soft. Do that again.
- 没错 我们是该跟罗斯谈谈   - 是
- Yeah, we need to talk to Ross. Yeah.     - Yeah.
- 嘿 你们准备好了没？ - 嗨
- Hey. You guys ready to go?     - Hey.
还没 摩妮卡还在发廊里 我正在打包
Not quite. Monica's at the salon, and I'm finishing packing.
老兄 你不把《圣经》带走吗？
Dude, you're not taking your Bible?
那是不能带走的
You're not supposed to take that.
再说 那是《新约》 你要拿来做什么？
Besides, it's a New Testament. What are you gonna do with it?
看看耶稣的底细
Learn about Jesus.
- 嗨   - 你跟乔伊谈过了吗？
- Hey!     - So did you talk to Joey?
还没 我没找到他 在飞机上我会跟他谈的
Uh, no. I couldn't find him. I'm just gonna talk to him on the plane.
这主意听起来不错 盖勒博士
Okay. Sounds like a good idea, Dr. Geller.
别说了
Stop it.
博士学位
Ph.D.
你真是太下流了
You're filthy.
你们看到摩妮卡了吗？
Hey. Have you guys seen Monica?
我想她去发廊了
Uh, actually, I think she went to the salon.
好吧 是的 她去发廊了
Oh, yeah. Oh, she went to the salon, all right.
大家看好了
Check it out!
看看谁走运了？
Whose day just got better?
钱德
Chandler!
嘿 啊
Hey! Aah.
- 你觉得如何？ - 我觉得…
- What do you think?     - I think...
- 我觉得可以看见你的头皮了   - 哈 哈
- I think I can see your scalp.     - Ha, ha.
你们不喜欢吗？
Don't you just love it?
喜欢… 你头上有贝壳
Yeah. Yeah, you got shellfish in your head.
那是 真有一套 太棒了 朋友
It's, uh, something. You go, girlfriend.
- 你这辈子从没这么说过吧   - 从来没有
- You never said that in your life.    - Not once.
我也这么觉得
I thought so.
你们听听看
Oh, and listen to this.
真出人意料 不只是视觉享受 这还是听觉享受
What do you know? It's a treat for the eyes and the ears.
噢
Ooh.
分手以后坐在查莉旁边有点尴尬
Wow, it's, uh, kind of weird that I'm sitting next to Charlie after we broke up.
巴贝多航空对你的社交生活 还真是不太贴
Yeah. It's almost as if Air Barbados doesn't care about your social life.
有人愿意跟我换位子 坐在查莉旁边吗？
Does someone mind switching and sitting with Charlie?
老兄 我… 我跟查莉 整个会议都在一起了
Oh, I mean, I... Dude, I spent the whole conference with Charlie.
- 我了解   - 不 我跟你换
- I understand.     - No, I'll do it.
希望我能换座位 我可不想跟亚伦艾佛森一起坐
Wish I could switch. I really don't want to sit with Allen lverson over there.
等升空后 机长解除安全带灯号后
Um, once we're in the air and the captain turns off the seat belt sign...
你可以在我的机舱内自由走动
...you feel free to roam about my cabin.
你在打开头顶置物箱时请小心
And you should be careful when checking your overhead bins.
- 因为物品在飞行中…   - 你真的不擅长这个
- Because items may shift during...     - Oh, you're not good at this.
- 你今晚要回家吗？ - 不用 我应该可以过去
- Do you have to go home tonight?    - No, I think I could come over.
- 今天是星期六吧   - 喔
- It's Saturday, right?     - Oh.
怎么了？
What?
- 我今晚不行   - 为什么？
- Um, I can't do anything tonight.    - Why not?
- 我有个约会   - 什…
- I have a date.    - Wh...?
- 你有约会？跟谁？ - 我的女朋友
- You have a date? With who?    - Oh, it's my girlfriend.
- 你有个女朋友？ - 对
- You have a girlfriend?    - Yeah.
我们两个分手以后 我开始跟别人交拄
Well, when you and I broke up, I started seeing someone.
- 那么 交往了多久？ - 三个月
- Well, for how long?    - Three months.
三个月？
Three months?
好吧
Okay.
这可能不干我的事 但你要继续跟她交往多久？
This is none of my business, but, um, how long are you gonna keep seeing her?
今天的晚餐中我会告诉她 说我们结束了 我保证
I'll tell her that it's over tonight at dinner. I promise.
好 很好 你就这么做
Oh, okay, good. You do that.
当你回家的时候 会有个专送的包裹等着你
When you get home, maybe there'll be a special delivery package waiting for you.
我也许会签名 撕闲包裹
Maybe I'll sign for it, tear it open.
- 把包装的东西全部扯开…   - 我们会上床 别再说了
- Pull out the packing material...    - We'll have sex. Let's leave it there.
好 我要去跟乔伊谈谈了 现在应该是时候了
All right, I'm gonna go talk to Joey. I think this is the right time.
在空中小姐说出"免税"之后 他的心情总是很好
He's in a good mood after the flight attendant says "duty-free."
好吧 祝你好运
Okay. Good luck.
罗斯正要过来 我想是时候跟他谈谈了
Ross is coming over. I think now would be a good time to talk to him.
我想应该是 但是… 我好紧张
Oh, I guess so. I'm just... I'm really nervous.
这样想好了 等你谈完了以后
Well, keep in mind that by the time you're done...
可能就是吃晚餐的时间了
...they'll probably be serving dinner.
噢
Ooh.
还紧张吗？
Still nervous?
我要点千层面
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
- 瑞秋   - 什么事？
- Hey, Rach, uh...     - Yeah?
- 我可以在这里坐一下吗？ - 可以 当然可以
- Do you mind if I sit here for a sec?    - Yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
祝你好运
Good luck.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hey. Ha.     - Hey.
我…
So I, um...
我必须跟你谈谈查莉的事情
I kind of need to talk to you about Charlie.
- 是吗？ - 昨晚 你们分手以后
- Yeah?    - Last night, after you guys broke up...
- 顺便一提 我很遗憾   - 呃 是
- So sorry to hear about that, by the way.    - Hmm, yeah.
查莉跟我在聊天 然后…
Well, Charlie and I were talking, and...
这个嘛…
Well...
- 你们亲嘴了   - 什…？
- You kissed.     - Wh...?
什么？
What? Ha, ha.
什么？你怎么会这样想？
What? Ha, ha. What would give you that idea?
- 我看到了   - 对 我们亲嘴了
- I saw you.     - Yeah, we kissed.
但其他什么都没发生 好吗？
But nothing else. Nothing else happened, okay?
- 罗斯… 没关系的   - 什么？
- Ross, Ross, Ross. It's okay.     - What?
没关系 听好了
It's okay. You know, look...
我完全了解 好吗 你们…
...I totally understand, all right? You guys...
你比我跟查莉还要相配
...make way more sense than her and I ever did, you know? And...
- 我希望你能快乐   - 你是说真的吗？
- I want you to be happy.     - Are you serious?
是
Yeah.
- 现在轮到我有些话…   - 我哑口无言了
- Now I have something...     - I am speechless.
你竟然把我的快乐 摆在第一位 我真的…
I mean, the fact that you would put my happiness first like that, I mean...
你真是个好朋友 你知道吗？
You're an incredible friend, do you know that?
- 听好了 在你走之前…   - 不 我是说真的
- Oh, well, look, before you go...     - No, I mean it.
你是那么地忠诚 无私又慷慨
I mean, you're so loyal, man. And selfless and generous.
对 我就是这样
I am those things, yeah.
因为我认识钱德比较久 所以一直觉得他是我最好的朋友 但是现在
I've known Chandler longer, so I think of him as my best friend. But now...
我得重新思考了
...I may have to rethink some stuff.
兄弟
Dude!
如果有任何我可以为你做的事…
Hey, if there is ever anything I can do for you...
我想不出有什么你可以做的
I can't think of anything. Ha, ha.
- 谢谢   - 不客气
- Thanks.     - Yeah.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- So hi.     - Hi.
- 所以你跟乔伊谈过了？ - 对 我们谈得很愉快
- So, you, uh, talked to Joey?     - Oh, yeah. We had a really good talk.
- 太好了   - 没错
- Oh, that's great.     - Yeah.
- 所以一切都没问题？ - 没问题 一切都太好了
- Oh. So everything's okay? Oh.    - Oh, no, it's great.
- 很好 他是个很棒的家伙   - 很显然地 我也这么觉得
- It's great. He's an amazing guy.     - Oh, well, obviously, I think so too.
我对这件事情感到很兴奋
Well, I'm so excited about this.
真的吗 兴奋？
Really? Ha, ha. Excited?
你在开玩笑吗？我甚至做过这种春梦
What, are you kidding? I have had some very dirty dreams about this.
失陪了
Excuse me.
你没告诉他对吧？
You didn't tell him, did you?
我没办法 他一直称赞我
I couldn't. He was saying all these really nice things about me.
我不能让他生气 收回那些话
I didn't want him to get mad and take them back.
- 不然我会被钱德比下去   - 噢 天哪
- I'm gonna edge out Chandler!     - Oh, God.
算了 乔伊 等我们回到纽约 我来告诉他好了
Fine. Forget it. When we go back to New York, I will tell him.
谢谢 很感谢你这么做
Thank you. Yeah, I appreciate that.
- 嗨 这是麦克的家   - 我是麦克
- Hi, Mike's place.     - Hey, it's Mike.
这么快
Ooh, that was fast.
不 她还没到
Oh, uh, no, she's not here yet.
我想我还是离开 在电话中跟她分手好了
You know, I'm just gonna take off and break up with her over the phone.
你不能这样 拜托 麦克 要有骨气一点
You can't do that. Oh, come on, Mike, strap on a pair.
难道你就不能说我们复合了？女人喜欢诚实的男人
Why don't you tell her that we got back together. Women appreciate honesty.
只是让你知道 我们偶尔 也喜欢被轻轻地打屁股
We also appreciate gentle spanking once in a while, just FYI.
另一件事 茶几上应该有珍爱的照片
One more thing. There might be a picture of Precious on my coffee table.
她的名字叫作"珍爱"？
Her name's Precious?
她是纯种的吗？还是在动物之家领养的？
Is she a pure breed, or did you pick her up at the pound? Ha, ha.
我只是想要让你知道
I just want to give you a heads-up.
好 如果她难过的话
Okay. And if she gets upset...
只要抓抓她的肚子 轻轻抓抓肝脏的部位就行了
...just scratch her tummy and give her a liver snap.
嗨 我是珍爱 你是谁？
Hi. I'm Precious. Who are you?
- 我是菲比   - 菲比？
- I'm... I'm Phoebe.     - Phoebe?
麦克的前女友？他此生的最爱那个菲比？
Mike's ex-girlfriend, Phoebe? The love of his life? That Phoebe?
我等不及让同事们看看了
Oh, I can't wait for everyone at work to see these!
哦
Ow!
- 你明天晚上要去工作对吧？ - 对
- You go back to work tomorrow night?     - Yeah.
如果你想让大家看到
So if you want people to see them...
那么你明天早上 就不会把那些拿掉对吧？
...you're not having them taken out, say, at the break of dawn?
如果我把这些拿掉的话 就不能这样做了
Well, if I had them taken out, then I wouldn't be able to do this.
嗯
Mm.
啊 啊
Aah! Aah!
你喜欢吧
You like that, right?
- 你在唱什么？ - 《第十号交响曲》的《波丽露》
- What are you singing?     - It's "Bolero" from 10.
不对 那是《现代敔示录》里的 《女武神的飞行》
It's "Ride of the Valkyries" from Apocalypse Now.
听着 辫子头可以解决 你头发毛躁的问题
Here's the thing. The cornrows were a solution to your frizzy-hair problem.
但是我们已经在家里了 你的头发也不会毛躁 所以麻烦你…
Now that we're home, you don't have that problem. If you think about it...
我很不喜欢
I hate them.
- 什么？你说你喜欢的   - 是吗？我们来回想一下
- What? You said you liked them.     - Did I? Let's refresh.
我相信我说的是 "我可以看见你的头皮了"
I believe what I said was that I could see your scalp.
好吧 你不喜欢又怎样 其他人都喜欢
Well, fine. So you don't like them. Everybody else does.
我们再一次来回想好了
Again, let's journey back.
我记得瑞秋说的是 她从来不知道你头壳的形状
As I recall, Rachel said she had never noticed the shape of your skull before.
乔伊呢 算了 他根本没发现有不同的地方
And Joey? Well, Joey didn't realize there was anything different.
你知道吗 我不在乎 我喜欢 所以我要留着
You know what? I don't care. I like it, and I'm gonna keep it.
你只是嫉妒罢了 因为你的头发不能这样
You're just jealous because your hair can't do this.
哦
Ow!
- 打到自己的牙齿了吗？ - 还有眼睛
- Get yourself in the tooth?    - And the eye.
你好 艾玛 你来了 天啊 我好想你
Hi! There she is! Hi, Emma. Oh, my God, I missed you.
艾玛 我好想你
Oh, Emma, I missed you so much. Hi.
你跟葛林外婆玩得开心吗？
Did you have a good time with Grandma Green? Huh?
她又给你抗忧郁剂瓶子当玩具了吗？
Did she give you a bottle of antidepressants again to use as a rattle?
只有一次而已 罗斯 而且只有五毫克
That was one time, Ross, and they were only, like, five milligrams.
艾玛 爸爸有个礼物要给你 好吧？
Ooh, hey, Emma, Daddy has some presents for you, okay?
你在这里等着
I want you to wait right here.
- 过来这里 小甜心   - 噢
- Come here, sweetie.     - Oh.
罗斯 其实我有件事…
Ross, um, actually, there's something that, uh...
要跟你谈谈
...I really need to talk to you about.
好 你说吧
Okay, shoot.
好吧 事情是这样的
Okay. Um, all right, here's the deal.
不 糟了
Ah! Oh, no!
- 怎么了？ - 洗发液大爆炸
- What is it?     - Oh, major shampoo explosion!
- 罗斯 这很不好开口   - 所有东西都沾到了
- Uh, look, Ross, this really isn't easy.     - Oh, it's all over everything!
为什么？为什么是我？
Why? Why me?
因为你拿了三百瓶洗发液？
Because you took 300 bottles of shampoo?
对不起 你刚刚说到哪里了？
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You were saying?
好
Well, yeah, uh...
- 听着 是有关于我跟…   - 不要又来了
- Look, it's about me and...     - Oh, not another one!
天啊 这是乳液 这个更难清洗
Oh, my God... Oh, and this is moisturizer! It's even harder to clean!
为什么 为什么坏事 总发生在好人身上？
Why? Why do bad things happen to good people?
- 显然现在不是个好时机   - 还用说
- Wow. Clearly this is not a good time.     - Uh, you think?
好吧 再见
Okay. Bye.
好 麦克正在过来的路上
All right, so Mike's on his way over.
你以为要在这里见面 他以为你们约在餐厅
You thought you were meeting here, he thought at the restaurant, so...
这没有谁对谁错 重要的是我要离开了
It doesn't matter who's right or wrong. The point is, I'm gonna take off.
在你告诉我发生什么事情之前 我是不会让你走的
Wait. I'm not letting you leave until you tell me what's going on. I mean...
你们两个要和好了吗？
...are you guys getting back together or something?
好吧
All right.
苏西 我可以叫你苏西吗？
Susie... Can I call you Susie?
我的名字是珍爱
My name is Precious.
我说不出口
I can't say that.
苏西 我跟你直话直说了
Um, Susie, I'm gonna be straight with you.
麦克跟我复合了 而不幸地…
Mike and I are back together. And, um, unfortunately...
你和他之间的关系结束了
...that effectively ends your relationship with him.
他觉得很抱歉 并且希望 你之后的所有关系都能很幸运
He's very sorry about that, and wishes you the best of luck in all your endeavors.
我真是不敢相信 为什么这样？
I just can't believe this. Why?
- 我不…   - 他为什么要这样做
- Well, I don't...    - Why would he do this?
- 我有什么问题吗？ - 你什么问题都没有
- What's wrong with me?     - There's nothing wrong with you.
我现在到底要怎么办才好？
What the hell am I supposed to do now?
真该死 女人 振作一点好吗？
Damn it, woman! Pull yourself together!
看在老天的份上 有点自尊吧
Have some pride, for the love of God!
好吧 这女孩不喜欢坚强的爱
Okay, not a fan of the tough love.
不敢相信麦克竟然 没有给我任何征兆
I just can't believe that Mike didn't give me any warning.
他并不知道 他也没有计划 要来巴贝多然后跟我求婚
He didn't know. He wasn't planning on coming to Barbados and proposing to me.
他跟你求婚了？这真是最糟糕的生日了
He proposed to you? This is the worst birthday ever!
听着 珍爱…
Look, Precious...
麦克不值得你这样 你是个有魅力又聪明的女人
Mike's not worth this. You're an attractive, intelligent woman...
面对现实吧 麦克有点烂
...and let's face it, Mike's kind of a wang.
他还跟你在一起就跟我求婚
He proposed to me while he was still seeing you.
他还在你生日当天要跟你分手？
He was gonna break up with you on your birthday?
我不想得了便宜还卖乖 但他这周末骗你的可多了
I don't like to kiss and tell, but he cheated on you a lot this weekend.
天啊 我想你说对了 也许我真的不需要他
Oh, my God, you know, maybe you're right. Maybe I don't need him.
我需要被尊重地对待
I deserve to be treated with respect.
去死吧 麦克 你这个懦夫混蛋 希望你下地狱
Screw you, Mike. You're a coward and a bastard, and I hope you rot in hell!
不客气
You're welcome.
亲爱的 你在里面待了好久 你还好吧？
Honey? You've been in there for a long time. Is everything okay?
不怎么好
Not really.
我有个麻烦
I have a problem.
真的吗 怎么了？
Really? What happened?
我边跳舞边唱着 《没女人 没眼泪》
Well, I was dancing around and singing "No Woman, No Cry"...
然后我被卡住了
...and, um, I got stuck.
- 你完全不能动吗？ - 我当然可以动
- You can't move at all?     - Oh, I can move. Ha, ha.
如果我帮你解开 请你去把辫子头弄掉好吗？
If I untangle you, will you please get rid of the cornrows?
我想应该可以
I guess so.
- 看起来有点磨损   - 我试着把它咬开
- Some of these look a little frayed.     - Yeah, I tried to gnaw myself free.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hey.     - Hi.
- 你跟罗斯谈过了吗？ - 我有试过
- So? Did you, uh, tell Ross?    - Well, I tried...
但是后来他遭遇某种洗发液意外
...but then he had a shampoo-related emergency.
- 所以我想又轮到你了   - 不…
- So I guess now it's your turn again.    - No, no, no, no.
我想你来告诉他会比较好 女生做这种事比较容易
I think it's better if you tell him. You know, it's easier for a woman.
如果他生气的话 你只要说
That way, you know, if he gets mad, all you have to do is go:
"我不是故意的"
"I didn't mean it.
"我真的很抱歉"
I'm so sorry."
对 我们就是那么做的
Yeah, because that's what we do.
好吧 那么这样吧 明天…
All right, all right, okay. Um, how about this? How about this? Tomorrow...
嗯？
Mm-hm?
明天我们一起去告诉他
Tomorrow we'll both go and we'll tell him together.
好 听起来很公平
Okay, that sounds fair.
- 这表示 我们又一次不能…   - 我知道
- That just means, once again, we can't...     - I know.
没关系的 我们会自我克制 我们又不是动物
That's okay. I mean, we can control ourselves. We're not animals.
- 当然 我们可以等的   - 对
- No! Pfft. Of course, we can wait.     - Yeah.
好吧 那么就晚安了
All right, so I guess that means good night then.
好 晚安
Yep. Good night.
哦
Oh.
晚安
Good night.
- 真的 晚安了   - 别再说晚安了
- Good night.     - Stop saying good night.
好的
Okay.
我真的好对不起
I'm so sorry.
看我在抽屉里找到了什么？
Look what I found in the drawer.
你还说我永远不会戴这顶帽子
And you said I'd never wear this.
不是要跟你邀功 可以为我做一件事情吗？
Now that I untangled you, how about you do a little something for me?
- 当然 你想要我做什么事情？ - 我想你知道
- Sure. What did you have in mind?    - I think you know.
- 真的吗 我真的不太想做   - 这就是我想要的
- Really? I don't... I don't really feel like it.     - This is what I want to do.
好吧
Okay.
真不知道你怎么那么喜欢
I just don't get why you like it so much.
她可是参加选美会 卧底的调查局探员呢
She's an FBI agent posing as a beauty contestant!